<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UNESCO World Heritage Site on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/unesco-world-heritage-site/</link><description>Recent content in UNESCO World Heritage Site on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/unesco-world-heritage-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angkor Thom</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</guid><description>Angkor Thom (meaning &amp;ldquo;Great City&amp;rdquo;) located in present-day Cambodia, was the last and most enduring capital city of the Khmer Empire. It was established in the late twelfth century by King Jayavarman VII. It covers an area of 9 km², within which are located several monuments from earlier eras as well as those established by Jayavarman and his successors. At the centre of the city is Jayavarman&amp;rsquo;s state temple, the Bayon, with the other major sites clustered around the Victory Square immediately to the north.</description></item><item><title>Angkor Wat</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</guid><description>Angkor Wat is a temple complex in Cambodia and the largest religious monument in the world. It was originally constructed in early 12th century as a Hindu temple for the Khmer Empire, gradually transforming into a Buddhist temple at the end of the 12th century. The temple is famed for the harmony of its design and extensive decoration that is integrated with the architecture. Virtually all of its surfaces, columns, lintels and even roofs are carved to illustrate scenes from Indian literature.</description></item><item><title>Cappadocia</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</guid><description>In a spectacular landscape, entirely sculpted by erosion, the Göreme valley and its surroundings contain rock-hewn sanctuaries that provide unique evidence of Byzantine art in the post-Iconoclastic period. The density of its rock-hewn dwellings, churches, troglodyte villages and subterranean cities within the rock formations make it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most striking and largest cave-dwelling complexes. Though interesting from a geological and ethnological point of view, the incomparable beauty of the decor of the Christian sanctuaries makes Cappadocia one of the leading examples of the post-iconoclastic Byzantine art period, some dating back to the 4th century.</description></item><item><title>Cinque Terre</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</guid><description>The Cinque Terre (The Five Lands) is a rugged portion of coast on the Italian Riviera. The five lands comprises five villages: Monterosso al Mare, Vernazza, Corniglia, Manarola, and Riomaggiore. The coastline, the five villages, and the surrounding hillsides are all part of the Cinque Terre National Park (Parco Nazionale delle Cinque Terre). Over the centuries, people have carefully built terraces on the rugged, steep landscape right up to the cliffs that overlook the sea.</description></item><item><title>Giant's Causeway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</guid><description>The Giant&amp;rsquo;s Causeway is an area of about 40,000 interlocking basalt columns, the result of an ancient volcanic fissure eruption. It is located in County Antrim on the north coast of Northern Ireland, about three miles (4.8 km) northeast of the town of Bushmills.</description></item><item><title>Grand Place</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</guid><description>La Grand Place (Grote Markt in Dutch) is the iconic central square in the Belgian capital Brussels. The square is surrounded by the city&amp;rsquo;s Town Hall, nearly forty guildhalls and other beautiful buildings from the 14th to 17th century. It is a UNESCO World Heritage site, and is widely considered the most beautiful town square in Europe. Every two years in August, an enormous flower carpet is set up in La Grand Place for a few days.</description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.</description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Mont Saint-Michel</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</guid><description>A magical island topped by a gravity-defying medieval monastery, the Mont-Saint-Michel counts among France’s most stunning sights. For centuries one of Europe’s major pilgrimage destinations, this holy mount is now a UNESCO World Heritage Site, as is its breathtaking bay.</description></item><item><title>Petra Raqmu</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</guid><description>Petra is a historical and archaeological city in southern Jordan that is famed for architecture carved directly into vibrant red, white, pink, and sandstone cliff faces. Originally known as Raqmu to the Nabataeans, Petra was the capital of the Nabataean empire until it was conquered and absorbed by the Roman Empire. The spectacular rock cut facades and innovative water conduit system found in Petra are monuments to the thriving and advanced civilization that once resided here.</description></item></channel></rss>