<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mountains on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/mountains/</link><description>Recent content in Mountains on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/mountains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ausangate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</guid><description>Also called &amp;ldquo;The Painted Mountains&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Rainbow Mountains&amp;rdquo; one look at them tells you where they get their name. These gorgeous pastel-colored mountains require a several day long trek through rough terrain, but it&amp;rsquo;s well worth it for the view!</description></item><item><title>Baatara gorge waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</guid><description>The Balaa gorge sinkhole (Baatara gorge waterfall) is a waterfall in the Tannourine, Lebanon near Balaa.
The waterfall drops 255 metres (837 ft) into the Balaa Pothole, a cave of Jurassic limestone located on the Lebanon Mountain Trail. The cave is also known as the Cave of the Three Bridges. Traveling from Laklouk to Tannourine one passes the village of Balaa, and the Three Bridges Chasm (in French Gouffre des Trois Ponts) is a five-minute journey into the valley below where one sees three natural bridges, rising one above the other and overhanging a chasm descending into Mount Lebanon.</description></item><item><title>Cappadocia</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</guid><description>In a spectacular landscape, entirely sculpted by erosion, the Göreme valley and its surroundings contain rock-hewn sanctuaries that provide unique evidence of Byzantine art in the post-Iconoclastic period. The density of its rock-hewn dwellings, churches, troglodyte villages and subterranean cities within the rock formations make it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most striking and largest cave-dwelling complexes. Though interesting from a geological and ethnological point of view, the incomparable beauty of the decor of the Christian sanctuaries makes Cappadocia one of the leading examples of the post-iconoclastic Byzantine art period, some dating back to the 4th century.</description></item><item><title>Cinque Terre</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</guid><description>The Cinque Terre (The Five Lands) is a rugged portion of coast on the Italian Riviera. The five lands comprises five villages: Monterosso al Mare, Vernazza, Corniglia, Manarola, and Riomaggiore. The coastline, the five villages, and the surrounding hillsides are all part of the Cinque Terre National Park (Parco Nazionale delle Cinque Terre). Over the centuries, people have carefully built terraces on the rugged, steep landscape right up to the cliffs that overlook the sea.</description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.</description></item><item><title>Jade Mountain Resort</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</guid><description>On 243 hectares of lush tropical hillside, this high-end resort is set on Anse Chastanet Beach, overlooking the Caribbean Sea, and is 4 km from St. Lucia Botanical Gardens.</description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Lake Louise</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/louise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/louise/</guid><description>Lake Louise has become symbolic of the quintessentially Canadian mountain scene. This alpine lake, known for its sparkling blue waters, is situated at the base of impressive glacier-clad peaks that have long been at the heart of Canadian mountaineering. At about 2.5 kilometres long and 90 metres deep, the lake offers a surreal paddling experience in the warm summer months and one of the most scenic skating rinks in the world in winter.</description></item><item><title>Lauterbrunnen</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lauterbrunnen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lauterbrunnen/</guid><description>Lauterbrunnen is a small village in the Bernese Oberland region of Switzerland nestled between the towering walls of a sheer-sided valley that is famed for its waterfalls.</description></item><item><title>Limone Sul Garda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</guid><description>Nestled in the Italian Alps is Lake Garda, the largest lake in Italy. Around the lake there are a few quaint and very popular tourist towns including one called Limone (meaning Lemon in Italian). In addition to the surrounding beauty of the alps themselves, the town features an abundance of lemon trees which are as beautiful as the products made from them are delicious. Whether you want to buy some limoncello or enjoy some lemonade at a restaurant on the coast of the lake, this town is a must visit.</description></item><item><title>Lungern</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lungern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lungern/</guid><description>Nestled in the canton of Obwalden, on the road between Lucerne and Interlaken, you’ll find the mountain town of Lungern. This natural paradise, surrounded by mountain trails, is the perfect destination for nature lovers and hikers alike.</description></item><item><title>Mayon Volcano</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mayon-volcano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mayon-volcano/</guid><description>This active stratovolcano is part of a national park &amp;amp; has erupted numerous times since 2000.</description></item><item><title>Mount Fuji</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</guid><description>Mount Fuji, Japan, is one of the most famous mountains in the world. Mount Fuji is a composite cone, or stratovolcano. Composite cones, formed by violent eruptions, have layers of rock, ash, and lava.</description></item><item><title>Narai</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</guid><description>Located between Kiso Fukushima and Matsumoto, Narai-juku is one of the best-preserved post towns on Kiso&amp;rsquo;s Nakasendo Trail. Visit for a taste of the Japan of old.</description></item><item><title>Natchez Trace Parkway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/natchez-trace-parkway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/natchez-trace-parkway/</guid><description>The Natchez Trace Parkway is a 444-mile recreational road and scenic drive through three states. It roughly follows the &amp;ldquo;Old Natchez Trace&amp;rdquo; a historic travel corridor used by American Indians, &amp;ldquo;Kaintucks,&amp;rdquo; European settlers, slave traders, soldiers, and future presidents. Today, people can enjoy not only a scenic drive but also hiking, biking, horseback riding, and camping along the parkway.
The Sunken Trace is one of the most photographed sites along the Parkway.</description></item><item><title>Ouzoud Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</guid><description>Ouzoud Falls is the collective name for several tall waterfalls that empty into the El-Abid River gorge. This popular tourism destination is located near the Middle Atlas village of Tanaghmeilt, in the province of Azilal, 150 km northeast of Marrakech, Morocco.</description></item><item><title>Panorama road between Waltensburg and Breil</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/waltensburg-breil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/waltensburg-breil/</guid><description>Panorama road between Waltensburg / Vuorz and Breil/Brigels, Canton of Grisons, Switzerland. Carved out passage.</description></item><item><title>Petra Raqmu</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</guid><description>Petra is a historical and archaeological city in southern Jordan that is famed for architecture carved directly into vibrant red, white, pink, and sandstone cliff faces. Originally known as Raqmu to the Nabataeans, Petra was the capital of the Nabataean empire until it was conquered and absorbed by the Roman Empire. The spectacular rock cut facades and innovative water conduit system found in Petra are monuments to the thriving and advanced civilization that once resided here.</description></item><item><title>Rigi</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/rigi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/rigi/</guid><description>Mount Rigi occupies a prominent place in the history of tourism. It has attracted tourists from around the world for nearly 150 years. Prior to 1871, people ascended Mount Rigi by foot or were carried in sedan chairs. In 1871, when the Rigi Railway from Vitznau started operating, reaching the summit of Mount Rigi became more comfortable and accessible for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Stelvio Pass</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/stelvio-pass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/stelvio-pass/</guid><description>This famous paved mountain pass used by drivers &amp;amp; cyclists features dozens of hairpin turns.</description></item><item><title>Valle de Cocora</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</guid><description>The wax palm, the Colombian national tree, is obviously the main attraction here. It is the tallest palm in the world, growing up to 60 meters, while retaining the girth of any old palm, making for a very slender giant, an immense pole topped with a little crown of palm fronds. Their wide root systems make for an odd visual: palms shooting up hundreds of feet into the sky, all widely but evenly spaced apart, as if planted purposefully.</description></item></channel></rss>