<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beach on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/beach/</link><description>Recent content in Beach on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apella Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/apella-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/apella-beach/</guid><description>Backed by a mountain with pine trees, this scenic beach offers clear water &amp;amp; chair/umbrella rentals.</description></item><item><title>Benagil Sea Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</guid><description>The southern coast of Portugal is lined with exquisite beaches and caves, including the famous Benagil Sea Cave (skylight included).</description></item><item><title>Blue Grotto</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</guid><description>The Blue cave is located in the small bay of Balun on the island of Biševo.
It is 24 m long, 10-12 meters wide, 15 inches tall and 16 m deep. The entrance to the cave is about 1.5 m high and about 2.5 m wide with a long sea corridor.
The cave has two openings, one smaller, one artificially deepened, through which the boat can pass. The other opening is like a vault and much wider, on the south side of the cave, below the sea level.</description></item><item><title>Galapinhos Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/galapinhos-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/galapinhos-beach/</guid><description>Remote beach in Arrábida Natural Park with calm waters &amp;amp; cliffs, accessible via a shuttle service.</description></item><item><title>Jökulsárlón Ice Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</guid><description>Jökulsárlón (literally &amp;ldquo;glacial river lagoon&amp;rdquo;) is a large glacial lake in southeast Iceland, on the edge of Vatnajökull National Park. Situated at the head of the Breiðamerkurjökull glacier, it developed into a lake after the glacier started receding from the edge of the Atlantic Ocean. The lake has grown since then at varying rates because of melting of the glaciers. It is now 1.5 kilometres (0.93 mi) away from the ocean&amp;rsquo;s edge and covers an area of about 18 km2 (6.</description></item><item><title>Kuramathi Island</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuramathi-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuramathi-island/</guid><description>Kuramathi is one of eight holiday resort islands owned and managed by Universal Enterprises Limited, a Maldivian company. There is a sandbank on the west of the island which is only visible when the tide is low.</description></item><item><title>Legzira Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</guid><description>The gigantic natural stone arches on this beach are indeed an amazing sight, although the beach itself is very rocky and as such does not lend itself well to sunbathing or swimming. Great for a walk though - the ocean is said to be as loud as an explosion when the waves crash against the rocks.</description></item><item><title>Little Manitou Lake</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/little-manitou-lake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/little-manitou-lake/</guid><description>This mineral lake known for its healing powers is so buoyant it&amp;rsquo;s been dubbed the &amp;ldquo;Dead Sea of Canada.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Musandam Governorate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</guid><description>The Norway of the middle east, in the sense that it has super arid desert fjords dip straight into the sea. Feels a bit like another planet.</description></item><item><title>Navagio Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shipwreck-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shipwreck-beach/</guid><description>Iconic pebble beach between towering cliffs with a shipwreck &amp;amp; turquoise water, reached by boat.</description></item><item><title>Sorrento Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/sorrento-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/sorrento-beach/</guid><description>Sorrento is a township in Victoria, Australia, located on the shores of Port Phillip on the Mornington Peninsula, about one and a half hours by car south of Melbourne. It is a largely upper-class, seaside resort area, but is also a quiet seaside township in the off-peak months of the year. It was named by the Italian founders after the southern Italian town.</description></item></channel></rss>