<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>US on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/us/</link><description>Recent content in US on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ellison's Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</guid><description>This pit cave is located on the Pigeon Mountain range on the Northwest of Georgia. It is the 12th deepest cave in the the US, extending over 12 miles and 1063 feet vertically. There are over 7 routes to reach the bottom of the cave.</description></item><item><title>Fort Jefferson</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/fort-jefferson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/fort-jefferson/</guid><description>Fort Jefferson is a massive but unfinished coastal fortress. It is the largest brick masonry structure in the Americas, and is composed of over 16 million bricks. The building covers 16 acres (6.5 ha). Among United States forts, only Fort Monroe in Virginia and Fort Adams in Rhode Island are larger. The fort is located on Garden Key in the lower Florida Keys within the Dry Tortugas National Park, 68 miles (109 km) west of the island of Key West.</description></item><item><title>Ginnie Springs</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ginnie-springs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ginnie-springs/</guid><description>Located on the Santa Fe River in High Springs Florida, Ginnie Springs is one of the clearest springs in Florida. The 72-degree water is perfect for river tubing, swimming, snorkeling, scuba and cave diving.</description></item><item><title>Havasu Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</guid><description>Waterfall on the Havasupai Indian Reservation, known for swimming in a dramatic blue-green pool.</description></item><item><title>Natchez Trace Parkway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/natchez-trace-parkway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/natchez-trace-parkway/</guid><description>The Natchez Trace Parkway is a 444-mile recreational road and scenic drive through three states. It roughly follows the &amp;ldquo;Old Natchez Trace&amp;rdquo; a historic travel corridor used by American Indians, &amp;ldquo;Kaintucks,&amp;rdquo; European settlers, slave traders, soldiers, and future presidents. Today, people can enjoy not only a scenic drive but also hiking, biking, horseback riding, and camping along the parkway.
The Sunken Trace is one of the most photographed sites along the Parkway.</description></item><item><title>Redwood National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</guid><description>At least once in your lifetime, you need to visit the magnificent coastal redwoods of Humboldt County - to walk, explore and soak up the silence and grandeur of forests unlike any others in the world. Whether your tastes run to scenic drives or hiking trails, you’ll find plenty of choices in Redwood National &amp;amp; State Parks in the north county, or along the Avenue of the Giants and Humboldt Redwoods State Park in south county.</description></item><item><title>Vermilion Cliffs National Monument</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/vermilion-cliffs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/vermilion-cliffs/</guid><description>Vermilion Cliffs National Monument is located in northern Coconino County, Arizona, United States, immediately south of the Utah state line. This national monument, 293,689 acres in area, protects the Paria Plateau, Vermilion Cliffs, Coyote Buttes, and Paria Canyon.</description></item></channel></rss>