<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KH on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/kh/</link><description>Recent content in KH on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/kh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angkor Thom</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</guid><description>&lt;p>Angkor Thom (meaning &amp;ldquo;Great City&amp;rdquo;) located in present-day Cambodia, was the last and most enduring capital city of the Khmer Empire. It was established in the late twelfth century by King Jayavarman VII. It covers an area of 9 km², within which are located several monuments from earlier eras as well as those established by Jayavarman and his successors. At the centre of the city is Jayavarman&amp;rsquo;s state temple, the Bayon, with the other major sites clustered around the Victory Square immediately to the north. The site is one of the major tourist attractions of southeast Asia.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Angkor Wat</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</guid><description>&lt;p>Angkor Wat is a temple complex in Cambodia and the largest religious monument in the world. It was originally constructed in early 12th century as a Hindu temple for the Khmer Empire, gradually transforming into a Buddhist temple at the end of the 12th century. The temple is famed for the harmony of its design and extensive decoration that is integrated with the architecture. Virtually all of its surfaces, columns, lintels and even roofs are carved to illustrate scenes from Indian literature.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>