<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JP on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/jp/</link><description>Recent content in JP on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/jp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mount Fuji</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mount Fuji, Japan, is one of the most famous mountains in the world. Mount Fuji is a composite cone, or stratovolcano. Composite cones, formed by violent eruptions, have layers of rock, ash, and lava.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Nara Deer Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nara Park (奈良公園, Nara Kōen) is a large park in central Nara. Established in 1880, it is the location of many of Nara&amp;rsquo;s main attractions including Todaiji, Kasuga Taisha, Kofukuji and the Nara National Museum. The park is home to hundreds of freely roaming deer. Considered in Shinto to be messengers of the gods, Nara&amp;rsquo;s nearly 1200 deer have become a symbol of the city and have even been designated as a natural treasure. Nara&amp;rsquo;s deer are surprisingly tame, although they can be aggressive if they think you will feed them. Deer crackers are for sale around the park, and some deer have learned to bow to visitors to ask to be fed.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Narai</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</guid><description>&lt;p>Located between Kiso Fukushima and Matsumoto, Narai-juku is one of the best-preserved post towns on Kiso&amp;rsquo;s Nakasendo Trail. Visit for a taste of the Japan of old.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>