<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ocean on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/ocean/</link><description>Recent content in Ocean on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/ocean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cinque Terre</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Cinque Terre (The Five Lands) is a rugged portion of coast on the Italian Riviera. The five lands comprises five villages: Monterosso al Mare, Vernazza, Corniglia, Manarola, and Riomaggiore. The coastline, the five villages, and the surrounding hillsides are all part of the Cinque Terre National Park (Parco Nazionale delle Cinque Terre). Over the centuries, people have carefully built terraces on the rugged, steep landscape right up to the cliffs that overlook the sea. Paths, trains and boats connect the villages. It is best to travel into Cinque Terre towns via train, as they are not entirely accessible by car.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Giant's Causeway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Giant&amp;rsquo;s Causeway is an area of about 40,000 interlocking basalt columns, the result of an ancient volcanic fissure eruption. It is located in County Antrim on the north coast of Northern Ireland, about three miles (4.8 km) northeast of the town of Bushmills.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hแบก Long Bay</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ha-long-bay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ha-long-bay/</guid><description>&lt;p>Multiple tree-covered limestone islands dot this scenic diving, rock climbing &amp;amp; hiking destination.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Legzira Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</guid><description>&lt;p>The gigantic natural stone arches on this beach are indeed an amazing sight, although the beach itself is very rocky and as such does not lend itself well to sunbathing or swimming. Great for a walk though - the ocean is said to be as loud as an explosion when the waves crash against the rocks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Shitiping</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shitiping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shitiping/</guid><description>&lt;p>Coastal spot popular for hiking &amp;amp; rock climbing, featuring a natural staircase of eroded stone.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>