<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GB on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/gb/</link><description>Recent content in GB on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/gb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eilean Donan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</guid><description>Eilean Donan is a small tidal island where three lochs meet, Loch Duich, Loch Long and Loch Alsh, in the western Highlands of Scotland. A picturesque castle that frequently appears in photographs, film and television dominates the island, which lies about 1 kilometre (0.62 mi) from the village of Dornie. Since the castle&amp;rsquo;s restoration in the early 20th century, a footbridge has connected the island to the mainland.</description></item><item><title>Giant's Causeway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</guid><description>The Giant&amp;rsquo;s Causeway is an area of about 40,000 interlocking basalt columns, the result of an ancient volcanic fissure eruption. It is located in County Antrim on the north coast of Northern Ireland, about three miles (4.8 km) northeast of the town of Bushmills.</description></item><item><title>White Cliffs of Dover</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dover/</guid><description>The White Cliffs of Dover are cliffs that form part of the English coastline facing the Strait of Dover and France. The cliffs are part of the North Downs formation. The cliff face, which reaches up to 350 feet (110 m), owes its striking façade to its composition of chalk accentuated by streaks of black flint. The cliffs spread east and west from the town of Dover in the county of Kent, an ancient and still important English port.</description></item></channel></rss>