<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cave on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/cave/</link><description>Recent content in Cave on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/cave/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benagil Sea Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</guid><description>The southern coast of Portugal is lined with exquisite beaches and caves, including the famous Benagil Sea Cave (skylight included).</description></item><item><title>Blue Grotto</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</guid><description>The Blue cave is located in the small bay of Balun on the island of Biševo.
It is 24 m long, 10-12 meters wide, 15 inches tall and 16 m deep. The entrance to the cave is about 1.5 m high and about 2.5 m wide with a long sea corridor.
The cave has two openings, one smaller, one artificially deepened, through which the boat can pass. The other opening is like a vault and much wider, on the south side of the cave, below the sea level.</description></item><item><title>Coober Pedy</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</guid><description>Coober Pedy is a town in southern Australia which around 150 million years ago was covered by ocean. When the water receded, the sandy silica minerals from the seabed flowed into the rocky cracks and cavities and solidified over time into the multi-coloured gem-stone, opal. Traditionally it has been a mining town ever since the discovery of opal, but the existing cavernous mines coupled with the intense heat outside made some people take a novel approach to building - going underground.</description></item><item><title>Ellison's Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</guid><description>This pit cave is located on the Pigeon Mountain range on the Northwest of Georgia. It is the 12th deepest cave in the the US, extending over 12 miles and 1063 feet vertically. There are over 7 routes to reach the bottom of the cave.</description></item><item><title>Sơn Đoòng Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/son-doong-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/son-doong-cave/</guid><description>According to the Limberts, the cave is five times larger than nearby caves like Phong Nha Cave and Hang En, the third largest cave in the world previously considered the biggest cave in Vietnam. The main passage in Sơn Đoòng is more than 5 kilometres (3.1 mi) long, 200 metres (660 ft) high and 150 metres (490 ft) wide.</description></item></channel></rss>