<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Middle-East on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/middle-east/</link><description>Recent content in Middle-East on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/middle-east/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Musandam Governorate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Norway of the middle east, in the sense that it has super arid desert fjords dip straight into the sea. Feels a bit like another planet.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Petra Raqmu</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Petra is a historical and archaeological city in southern Jordan that is famed for architecture carved directly into vibrant red, white, pink, and sandstone cliff faces. Originally known as Raqmu to the Nabataeans, Petra was the capital of the Nabataean empire until it was conquered and absorbed by the Roman Empire. The spectacular rock cut facades and innovative water conduit system found in Petra are monuments to the thriving and advanced civilization that once resided here.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Socotra</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</guid><description>&lt;p>One of the most striking of Socotra&amp;rsquo;s plants is the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood tree (Dracaena cinnabari), which is a strange-looking, umbrella-shaped tree. Its red sap was thought to be the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood of the ancients, sought after as a dye, and today used as paint and varnish. Also important in ancient times were Socotra&amp;rsquo;s various endemic aloes, used medicinally, and for cosmetics. Other endemic plants include the giant succulent tree Dorstenia gigas, the cucumber tree Dendrosicyos socotranus, the rare Socotran pomegranate, Aloe perryi, and Boswellia socotrana.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>