<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Waterfall on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/waterfall/</link><description>Recent content in Waterfall on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/waterfall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Haifoss Waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</guid><description>The waterfall Háifoss is situated near the volcano Hekla in the south of Iceland. The river Fossá, a tributary of Þjórsá, drops here from a height of 122 m. This is the second highest waterfall of the island.</description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.</description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Kuang Si Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</guid><description>The Kuang Si Falls, sometimes spelled Kuang Xi or known as Tat Kuang Si Waterfalls, is a three tier waterfall about 29 kilometres (18 mi) south of Luang Prabang. These waterfalls are a favourite side trip for tourists in Luang Prabang. The falls begin in shallow pools atop a steep hillside. These lead to the main fall with a 60 metres (200 ft)cascade. The falls are accessed via a trail to a left of the falls.</description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</guid><description>Famous, towering waterfalls at the boundary of Canada &amp;amp; the United States, with tours &amp;amp; boat rides.</description></item><item><title>Skógafoss</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</guid><description>Skógafoss is a waterfall situated on the Skógá River in the south of Iceland at the cliffs of the former coastline. After the coastline had receded seaward (it is now at a distance of about 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from Skógar), the former sea cliffs remained, parallel to the coast over hundreds of kilometres, creating together with some mountains a clear border between the coastal lowlands and the Highlands of Iceland.</description></item></channel></rss>