<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Waterfall on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/waterfall/</link><description>Recent content in Waterfall on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/waterfall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Baatara gorge waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Balaa gorge sinkhole (Baatara gorge waterfall) is a waterfall in the Tannourine, Lebanon near Balaa.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The waterfall drops 255 metres (837 ft) into the Balaa Pothole, a cave of Jurassic limestone located on the Lebanon Mountain Trail. The cave is also known as the Cave of the Three Bridges. Traveling from Laklouk to Tannourine one passes the village of Balaa, and the Three Bridges Chasm (in French Gouffre des Trois Ponts) is a five-minute journey into the valley below where one sees three natural bridges, rising one above the other and overhanging a chasm descending into Mount Lebanon. During the spring melt, a 90–100-metre (300–330 ft) cascade falls behind the three bridges and then down into the 240-metre (790 ft) chasm.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Furong Town</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/furong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/furong/</guid><description>&lt;p>Furong is a town in Yongshun County, Xiangxi Prefecture, Hunan. The town, also advertised as Furong Ancient Town, is a tourist attraction in mountainous northwest Hunan, approximately halfway between the popular tourist destinations of Fenghuang County and Zhangjiajie.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Haifoss Waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</guid><description>&lt;p>The waterfall Háifoss is situated near the volcano Hekla in the south of Iceland. The river Fossá, a tributary of Þjórsá, drops here from a height of 122 m. This is the second highest waterfall of the island.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Havasu Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</guid><description>&lt;p>Waterfall on the Havasupai Indian Reservation, known for swimming in a dramatic blue-green pool.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Kuang Si Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Kuang Si Falls, sometimes spelled Kuang Xi or known as Tat Kuang Si Waterfalls, is a three tier waterfall about 29 kilometres (18 mi) south of Luang Prabang. These waterfalls are a favourite side trip for tourists in Luang Prabang. The falls begin in shallow pools atop a steep hillside. These lead to the main fall with a 60 metres (200 ft)cascade. The falls are accessed via a trail to a left of the falls. The water collects in numerous turquoise blue pools as it flows downstream. The many cascades that result are typical of travertine waterfalls.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</guid><description>&lt;p>Famous, towering waterfalls at the boundary of Canada &amp;amp; the United States, with tours &amp;amp; boat rides.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ouzoud Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ouzoud Falls is the collective name for several tall waterfalls that empty into the El-Abid River gorge. This popular tourism destination is located near the Middle Atlas village of Tanaghmeilt, in the province of Azilal, 150 km northeast of Marrakech, Morocco.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Plitvice Lakes National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/plitvice-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/plitvice-lakes/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Plitvice Lakes is the oldest and the largest national park in the Republic of Croatia. The exceptional natural beauty of this area has always attracted nature lovers. As a result of that, it was declared the first national park of the Republic of Croatia as early as 8 April 1949. The process of tufa formation, through which tufa barriers and subsequently lakes are formed, is the outstanding universal value for which Plitvice Lakes received international recognition on 26 October 1979, when it was inscribed on the UNESCO World Heritage List.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skógafoss</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</guid><description>&lt;p>Skógafoss is a waterfall situated on the Skógá River in the south of Iceland at the cliffs of the former coastline. After the coastline had receded seaward (it is now at a distance of about 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from Skógar), the former sea cliffs remained, parallel to the coast over hundreds of kilometres, creating together with some mountains a clear border between the coastal lowlands and the Highlands of Iceland.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>