<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asian on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/asian/</link><description>Recent content in Asian on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/asian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angkor Wat</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</guid><description>Angkor Wat is a temple complex in Cambodia and the largest religious monument in the world. It was originally constructed in early 12th century as a Hindu temple for the Khmer Empire, gradually transforming into a Buddhist temple at the end of the 12th century. The temple is famed for the harmony of its design and extensive decoration that is integrated with the architecture. Virtually all of its surfaces, columns, lintels and even roofs are carved to illustrate scenes from Indian literature.</description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jodhpur/</guid><description>Jodhpur is also known as the Blue City, an apt name as most houses in the old city are shades of blue. This is particularly noticeable on the north side of the town, known as Brahmpuri for the many Brahmins that live there.</description></item><item><title>Kuang Si Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</guid><description>The Kuang Si Falls, sometimes spelled Kuang Xi or known as Tat Kuang Si Waterfalls, is a three tier waterfall about 29 kilometres (18 mi) south of Luang Prabang. These waterfalls are a favourite side trip for tourists in Luang Prabang. The falls begin in shallow pools atop a steep hillside. These lead to the main fall with a 60 metres (200 ft)cascade. The falls are accessed via a trail to a left of the falls.</description></item><item><title>Mù Cang Chải</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</guid><description>Mù Cang Chải manages to be one of the most breathtaking spots in Vietnam, with terraced rice fields and mountainous landscapes.</description></item><item><title>Nara Deer Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</guid><description>Nara Park (奈良公園, Nara Kōen) is a large park in central Nara. Established in 1880, it is the location of many of Nara&amp;rsquo;s main attractions including Todaiji, Kasuga Taisha, Kofukuji and the Nara National Museum. The park is home to hundreds of freely roaming deer. Considered in Shinto to be messengers of the gods, Nara&amp;rsquo;s nearly 1200 deer have become a symbol of the city and have even been designated as a natural treasure.</description></item></channel></rss>