<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HR on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/hr/</link><description>Recent content in HR on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/hr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blue Grotto</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Blue cave is located in the small bay of Balun on the island of Biševo.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It is 24 m long, 10-12 meters wide, 15 inches tall and 16 m deep. The entrance to the cave is about 1.5 m high and about 2.5 m wide with a long sea corridor.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The cave has two openings, one smaller, one artificially deepened, through which the boat can pass. The other opening is like a vault and much wider, on the south side of the cave, below the sea level. The underwater canopy through the cave floods the sunlight, which, passing through the water, first disappears, and then falls from the bottom of the cave, filling the entire cave with a silver-blue resin.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Plitvice Lakes National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/plitvice-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/plitvice-lakes/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Plitvice Lakes is the oldest and the largest national park in the Republic of Croatia. The exceptional natural beauty of this area has always attracted nature lovers. As a result of that, it was declared the first national park of the Republic of Croatia as early as 8 April 1949. The process of tufa formation, through which tufa barriers and subsequently lakes are formed, is the outstanding universal value for which Plitvice Lakes received international recognition on 26 October 1979, when it was inscribed on the UNESCO World Heritage List.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>