<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Man-Made on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/man-made/</link><description>Recent content in Man-Made on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/man-made/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angkor Thom</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-thom/</guid><description>&lt;p>Angkor Thom (meaning &amp;ldquo;Great City&amp;rdquo;) located in present-day Cambodia, was the last and most enduring capital city of the Khmer Empire. It was established in the late twelfth century by King Jayavarman VII. It covers an area of 9 km², within which are located several monuments from earlier eras as well as those established by Jayavarman and his successors. At the centre of the city is Jayavarman&amp;rsquo;s state temple, the Bayon, with the other major sites clustered around the Victory Square immediately to the north. The site is one of the major tourist attractions of southeast Asia.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Angkor Wat</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/angkor-wat/</guid><description>&lt;p>Angkor Wat is a temple complex in Cambodia and the largest religious monument in the world. It was originally constructed in early 12th century as a Hindu temple for the Khmer Empire, gradually transforming into a Buddhist temple at the end of the 12th century. The temple is famed for the harmony of its design and extensive decoration that is integrated with the architecture. Virtually all of its surfaces, columns, lintels and even roofs are carved to illustrate scenes from Indian literature.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bonn</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</guid><description>&lt;p>This German city has a fantastic display of cherry blossom trees when in season.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cinque Terre</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Cinque Terre (The Five Lands) is a rugged portion of coast on the Italian Riviera. The five lands comprises five villages: Monterosso al Mare, Vernazza, Corniglia, Manarola, and Riomaggiore. The coastline, the five villages, and the surrounding hillsides are all part of the Cinque Terre National Park (Parco Nazionale delle Cinque Terre). Over the centuries, people have carefully built terraces on the rugged, steep landscape right up to the cliffs that overlook the sea. Paths, trains and boats connect the villages. It is best to travel into Cinque Terre towns via train, as they are not entirely accessible by car.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Civita di Bagnoregio</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/civita-di-bagnoregio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/civita-di-bagnoregio/</guid><description>&lt;p>Civita di Bagnoregio is a hilltop village in central Italy. It’s accessed via a pedestrian bridge from the nearby ticket office in Bagnoregio village. The Porta Santa Maria gateway was built by the Etruscans. Founded in the 7th century, the Romanesque San Donato Church sits in the main square. Nearby is the Geological and Landslides Museum, whose exhibits document projects to shore up the village&amp;rsquo;s eroding hillside.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Coober Pedy</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Coober Pedy is a town in southern Australia which around 150 million years ago was covered by ocean. When the water receded, the sandy silica minerals from the seabed flowed into the rocky cracks and cavities and solidified over time into the multi-coloured gem-stone, opal. Traditionally it has been a mining town ever since the discovery of opal, but the existing cavernous mines coupled with the intense heat outside made some people take a novel approach to building - going underground.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dunbar Rock</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dunbar-rock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dunbar-rock/</guid><description>&lt;p>This beautiful historical landmark was once used as a mooring for the famous pirate Blackbeard. Local legend has it that there is buried treasure on the island. When the original owner was constructing the villas, he discovered a hidden cave on the island. He found many pieces of pre-Colombian pottery, but sadly no treasure. But he started construction on what would soon become a new jewel in the Caribbean.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Eilean Donan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</guid><description>&lt;p>Eilean Donan is a small tidal island where three lochs meet, Loch Duich, Loch Long and Loch Alsh, in the western Highlands of Scotland. A picturesque castle that frequently appears in photographs, film and television dominates the island, which lies about 1 kilometre (0.62 mi) from the village of Dornie. Since the castle&amp;rsquo;s restoration in the early 20th century, a footbridge has connected the island to the mainland.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fort Jefferson</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/fort-jefferson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/fort-jefferson/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fort Jefferson is a massive but unfinished coastal fortress. It is the largest brick masonry structure in the Americas, and is composed of over 16 million bricks. The building covers 16 acres (6.5 ha). Among United States forts, only Fort Monroe in Virginia and Fort Adams in Rhode Island are larger. The fort is located on Garden Key in the lower Florida Keys within the Dry Tortugas National Park, 68 miles (109 km) west of the island of Key West. The Dry Tortugas are part of Monroe County, Florida, United States.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Furong Town</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/furong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/furong/</guid><description>&lt;p>Furong is a town in Yongshun County, Xiangxi Prefecture, Hunan. The town, also advertised as Furong Ancient Town, is a tourist attraction in mountainous northwest Hunan, approximately halfway between the popular tourist destinations of Fenghuang County and Zhangjiajie.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Grand Place</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</guid><description>&lt;p>La Grand Place (Grote Markt in Dutch) is the iconic central square in the Belgian capital Brussels. The square is surrounded by the city&amp;rsquo;s Town Hall, nearly forty guildhalls and other beautiful buildings from the 14th to 17th century. It is a UNESCO World Heritage site, and is widely considered the most beautiful town square in Europe. Every two years in August, an enormous flower carpet is set up in La Grand Place for a few days. A million colorful begonias are set up in geometric patterns covering an area of 1,800 square meters.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Huacachina</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huacachina/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huacachina/</guid><description>&lt;p>Huacachina is a desert oasis and tiny village just west of the city of Ica in southwestern Peru. At its center are the green waters of the Huacachina Lagoon, ringed by palm trees and thought to have therapeutic properties. The lagoon&amp;rsquo;s shores are dotted with bars and clubs. Dune buggies run across the high, rolling sand dunes surrounding the village.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jade Mountain Resort</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</guid><description>&lt;p>On 243 hectares of lush tropical hillside, this high-end resort is set on Anse Chastanet Beach, overlooking the Caribbean Sea, and is 4 km from St. Lucia Botanical Gardens.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jodhpur</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jodhpur/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jodhpur is also known as the Blue City, an apt name as most houses in the old city are shades of blue. This is particularly noticeable on the north side of the town, known as Brahmpuri for the many Brahmins that live there.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Kawachi Fujien Garden</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kawachi-fujien-garden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kawachi-fujien-garden/</guid><description>&lt;p>Kawachi Fujien Garden (河内藤園) is a private garden in the wooded hills south of central Kitakyushu, famous for its spectacularly presented, large numbers of wisteria flowers. The garden&amp;rsquo;s most prominent features are two, roughly 100 meter long tunnels made of wisteria trees of differing varieties and colors, and a collection of large wisteria trees that together form an enormous roof of drooping flowers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lake Bled</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</guid><description>&lt;p>According to a legend which stayed with the people, the temple of the ancient Slavic goddess Živa, once stood in the place of the present Baroque church. The temple disappeared during battles between the followers of the pagan religion and Christians, who destroyed the altar and built a church.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Limone Sul Garda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nestled in the Italian Alps is Lake Garda, the largest lake in Italy. Around the lake there are a few quaint and very popular tourist towns including one called Limone (meaning Lemon in Italian). In addition to the surrounding beauty of the alps themselves, the town features an abundance of lemon trees which are as beautiful as the products made from them are delicious. Whether you want to buy some limoncello or enjoy some lemonade at a restaurant on the coast of the lake, this town is a must visit.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mont Saint-Michel</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</guid><description>&lt;p>A magical island topped by a gravity-defying medieval monastery, the Mont-Saint-Michel counts among France’s most stunning sights. For centuries one of Europe’s major pilgrimage destinations, this holy mount is now a UNESCO World Heritage Site, as is its breathtaking bay.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mù Cang Chải</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mù Cang Chải manages to be one of the most breathtaking spots in Vietnam, with terraced rice fields and mountainous landscapes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Neuschwanstein Castle</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/neuschwanstein-castle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/neuschwanstein-castle/</guid><description>&lt;p>Neuschwanstein Castle is a nineteenth-century Romanesque Revival palace on a rugged hill above the village of Hohenschwangau near Füssen in southwest Bavaria, Germany. The palace was commissioned by Ludwig II of Bavaria as a retreat and as an homage to Richard Wagner. Ludwig paid for the palace out of his personal fortune and by means of extensive borrowing, rather than Bavarian public funds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Odda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/odda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/odda/</guid><description>&lt;p>Odda municipality is very mountainous and the settlements are all located in valleys. Because of the many mountains, there are many large waterfalls including Låtefossen, Espelandsfossen, and Tyssestrengene. There are also many large lakes such as Sandvinvatnet, Votna, Valldalsvatnet, Røldalsvatnet, Ringedalsvatnet, Langavatnet, and parts of Ståvatn.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Palace of Versailles</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Palace of Versailles (château de Versailles) is a royal château in Versailles, some 20 kilometers southwest of Paris. The palace was built for the Bourbon kings of France in the 17th century, fell into disrepair following the French revolution, and is now a museum and tourist attraction. The palace exemplifies the opulence of the Ancien Régime and the extensive gardens are one of the finest extant examples of French garden design.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Panorama road between Waltensburg and Breil</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/waltensburg-breil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/waltensburg-breil/</guid><description>&lt;p>Panorama road between Waltensburg / Vuorz and Breil/Brigels, Canton of Grisons, Switzerland. Carved out passage.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Petra Raqmu</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Petra is a historical and archaeological city in southern Jordan that is famed for architecture carved directly into vibrant red, white, pink, and sandstone cliff faces. Originally known as Raqmu to the Nabataeans, Petra was the capital of the Nabataean empire until it was conquered and absorbed by the Roman Empire. The spectacular rock cut facades and innovative water conduit system found in Petra are monuments to the thriving and advanced civilization that once resided here.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Riwai</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/riwai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/riwai/</guid><description>&lt;p>This village features a unique bridge created by forcing tree roots to grow in a particular twisted pattern. The result is a living bridge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Royal Palace of Caserta</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Royal Palace of Caserta (Italian: Reggia di Caserta) is a former royal residence in Caserta, southern Italy, constructed for the Bourbon kings of Naples during the 18th century. The palace is a UNESCO World Heritage Site; its nomination described it as &amp;ldquo;the swan song of the spectacular art of the Baroque, from which it adopted all the features needed to create the illusions of multidirectional space&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>San Martin Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/san-martin-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/san-martin-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Parque General San Martín is a park located in the city of Mendoza, Argentina.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Széchenyi Thermal Bath</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/szechenyi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/szechenyi/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ornate thermal baths, built in 1913, with a cupola, massivve swimming pools &amp;amp; water jet massagers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Via Appia Antica</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/via-appia-antica/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/via-appia-antica/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Via Appica (Appian Way) was constructed in the 4th century B.C.; it is the reason we say all roads lead to Rome. The road is remarkably well preserved, its large flat paving stones polished by millennia of use and weathering, and standing as testament to the might of Roman engineering. Today the road is flanked on both sides by verdant fields punctuated with ruins and other vestiges of Roman history, with the occasional herds of grazing sheep adding to the sense of being transported back in time. Easily accessible from Rome, this free tourist attraction literally takes a trip down Rome&amp;rsquo;s memory lane.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>