<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flora on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/flora/</link><description>Recent content in Flora on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/flora/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bonn</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</guid><description>&lt;p>This German city has a fantastic display of cherry blossom trees when in season.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Limone Sul Garda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nestled in the Italian Alps is Lake Garda, the largest lake in Italy. Around the lake there are a few quaint and very popular tourist towns including one called Limone (meaning Lemon in Italian). In addition to the surrounding beauty of the alps themselves, the town features an abundance of lemon trees which are as beautiful as the products made from them are delicious. Whether you want to buy some limoncello or enjoy some lemonade at a restaurant on the coast of the lake, this town is a must visit.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Redwood National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>At least once in your lifetime, you need to visit the magnificent coastal redwoods of Humboldt County - to walk, explore and soak up the silence and grandeur of forests unlike any others in the world. Whether your tastes run to scenic drives or hiking trails, you’ll find plenty of choices in Redwood National &amp;amp; State Parks in the north county, or along the Avenue of the Giants and Humboldt Redwoods State Park in south county.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Socotra</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</guid><description>&lt;p>One of the most striking of Socotra&amp;rsquo;s plants is the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood tree (Dracaena cinnabari), which is a strange-looking, umbrella-shaped tree. Its red sap was thought to be the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood of the ancients, sought after as a dye, and today used as paint and varnish. Also important in ancient times were Socotra&amp;rsquo;s various endemic aloes, used medicinally, and for cosmetics. Other endemic plants include the giant succulent tree Dorstenia gigas, the cucumber tree Dendrosicyos socotranus, the rare Socotran pomegranate, Aloe perryi, and Boswellia socotrana.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Valle de Cocora</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</guid><description>&lt;p>The wax palm, the Colombian national tree, is obviously the main attraction here. It is the tallest palm in the world, growing up to 60 meters, while retaining the girth of any old palm, making for a very slender giant, an immense pole topped with a little crown of palm fronds. Their wide root systems make for an odd visual: palms shooting up hundreds of feet into the sky, all widely but evenly spaced apart, as if planted purposefully.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>