<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IS on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/is/</link><description>Recent content in IS on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/country/is/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Haifoss Waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</guid><description>The waterfall Háifoss is situated near the volcano Hekla in the south of Iceland. The river Fossá, a tributary of Þjórsá, drops here from a height of 122 m. This is the second highest waterfall of the island.</description></item><item><title>Hvítserkur</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</guid><description>Hvítserkur is a 15 m high basalt stack along the eastern shore of the Vatnsnes peninsula, in northwest Iceland. The rock has two holes at the base, which give it the appearance of a dragon who is drinking. The base of the stack has been reinforced with concrete to protect its foundations from the sea. Several species of birds, such as gulls and fulmars, live on at Hvítserkur and its name (&amp;ldquo;white shirt&amp;rdquo; in Icelandic) comes from the color of the guano deposited on its rocks.</description></item><item><title>Jökulsárlón Ice Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</guid><description>Jökulsárlón (literally &amp;ldquo;glacial river lagoon&amp;rdquo;) is a large glacial lake in southeast Iceland, on the edge of Vatnajökull National Park. Situated at the head of the Breiðamerkurjökull glacier, it developed into a lake after the glacier started receding from the edge of the Atlantic Ocean. The lake has grown since then at varying rates because of melting of the glaciers. It is now 1.5 kilometres (0.93 mi) away from the ocean&amp;rsquo;s edge and covers an area of about 18 km2 (6.</description></item><item><title>Skógafoss</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</guid><description>Skógafoss is a waterfall situated on the Skógá River in the south of Iceland at the cliffs of the former coastline. After the coastline had receded seaward (it is now at a distance of about 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from Skógar), the former sea cliffs remained, parallel to the coast over hundreds of kilometres, creating together with some mountains a clear border between the coastal lowlands and the Highlands of Iceland.</description></item></channel></rss>