<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Castle on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/castle/</link><description>Recent content in Castle on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/castle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eilean Donan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</guid><description>&lt;p>Eilean Donan is a small tidal island where three lochs meet, Loch Duich, Loch Long and Loch Alsh, in the western Highlands of Scotland. A picturesque castle that frequently appears in photographs, film and television dominates the island, which lies about 1 kilometre (0.62 mi) from the village of Dornie. Since the castle&amp;rsquo;s restoration in the early 20th century, a footbridge has connected the island to the mainland.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Grand Place</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/grand-place/</guid><description>&lt;p>La Grand Place (Grote Markt in Dutch) is the iconic central square in the Belgian capital Brussels. The square is surrounded by the city&amp;rsquo;s Town Hall, nearly forty guildhalls and other beautiful buildings from the 14th to 17th century. It is a UNESCO World Heritage site, and is widely considered the most beautiful town square in Europe. Every two years in August, an enormous flower carpet is set up in La Grand Place for a few days. A million colorful begonias are set up in geometric patterns covering an area of 1,800 square meters.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lake Bled</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</guid><description>&lt;p>According to a legend which stayed with the people, the temple of the ancient Slavic goddess Živa, once stood in the place of the present Baroque church. The temple disappeared during battles between the followers of the pagan religion and Christians, who destroyed the altar and built a church.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mont Saint-Michel</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</guid><description>&lt;p>A magical island topped by a gravity-defying medieval monastery, the Mont-Saint-Michel counts among France’s most stunning sights. For centuries one of Europe’s major pilgrimage destinations, this holy mount is now a UNESCO World Heritage Site, as is its breathtaking bay.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Neuschwanstein Castle</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/neuschwanstein-castle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/neuschwanstein-castle/</guid><description>&lt;p>Neuschwanstein Castle is a nineteenth-century Romanesque Revival palace on a rugged hill above the village of Hohenschwangau near Füssen in southwest Bavaria, Germany. The palace was commissioned by Ludwig II of Bavaria as a retreat and as an homage to Richard Wagner. Ludwig paid for the palace out of his personal fortune and by means of extensive borrowing, rather than Bavarian public funds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Palace of Versailles</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Palace of Versailles (château de Versailles) is a royal château in Versailles, some 20 kilometers southwest of Paris. The palace was built for the Bourbon kings of France in the 17th century, fell into disrepair following the French revolution, and is now a museum and tourist attraction. The palace exemplifies the opulence of the Ancien Régime and the extensive gardens are one of the finest extant examples of French garden design.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Royal Palace of Caserta</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Royal Palace of Caserta (Italian: Reggia di Caserta) is a former royal residence in Caserta, southern Italy, constructed for the Bourbon kings of Naples during the 18th century. The palace is a UNESCO World Heritage Site; its nomination described it as &amp;ldquo;the swan song of the spectacular art of the Baroque, from which it adopted all the features needed to create the illusions of multidirectional space&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>