<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remote on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/remote/</link><description>Recent content in Remote on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/remote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ausangate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</guid><description>Also called &amp;ldquo;The Painted Mountains&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Rainbow Mountains&amp;rdquo; one look at them tells you where they get their name. These gorgeous pastel-colored mountains require a several day long trek through rough terrain, but it&amp;rsquo;s well worth it for the view!</description></item><item><title>Coober Pedy</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</guid><description>Coober Pedy is a town in southern Australia which around 150 million years ago was covered by ocean. When the water receded, the sandy silica minerals from the seabed flowed into the rocky cracks and cavities and solidified over time into the multi-coloured gem-stone, opal. Traditionally it has been a mining town ever since the discovery of opal, but the existing cavernous mines coupled with the intense heat outside made some people take a novel approach to building - going underground.</description></item><item><title>Danakil Depression</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</guid><description>The lowest and hottest place on earth, but you&amp;rsquo;re rewarded with amazing imagery of sulphurous lakes and geological creations. Remote, but worth it.</description></item><item><title>Durban Island</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</guid><description>Durban Island is a Canadian Arctic island located in Nunavut, Canada. It is one of Baffin Island&amp;rsquo;s northeast offshore islands within Davis Strait&amp;rsquo;s Merchants Bay. It is 36 km2 (14 sq mi) in size. Durban Harbour is on the island&amp;rsquo;s southeast facing side. Nearby can be found the larger Padloping Island, and Auyuittuq National Park Reserve is also to the west on Baffin Island.</description></item><item><title>French Southern Territories</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/french-southern-and-antarctic-lands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/french-southern-and-antarctic-lands/</guid><description>The Southern Lands consist of two archipelagos, Iles Crozet and Iles Kerguelen, and two volcanic islands, Ile Amsterdam and Ile Saint-Paul. They have no permanent inhabitants and are visited only by researchers studying the native fauna. The &amp;ldquo;Antarctic Lands&amp;rdquo; portion consists of Adelie Land, a thin slice of the Antarctic continent discovered and claimed by the French in 1840, and set aside by the Antarctic Treaty.</description></item><item><title>Jökulsárlón Ice Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</guid><description>Jökulsárlón (literally &amp;ldquo;glacial river lagoon&amp;rdquo;) is a large glacial lake in southeast Iceland, on the edge of Vatnajökull National Park. Situated at the head of the Breiðamerkurjökull glacier, it developed into a lake after the glacier started receding from the edge of the Atlantic Ocean. The lake has grown since then at varying rates because of melting of the glaciers. It is now 1.5 kilometres (0.93 mi) away from the ocean&amp;rsquo;s edge and covers an area of about 18 km2 (6.</description></item><item><title>Leitisvatn Lake</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</guid><description>The name Leitisvatn means &amp;ldquo;The lake by Leiti&amp;rdquo; (the name of the east side of the lake). The lake is located very close to the ocean, but its surface is about 30 meters above the level of sea. It is surrounded by a higher cliff which prevents it from emptying into the ocean. The water exit is the waterfall Bøsdalafossur.</description></item></channel></rss>