<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nordic on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/nordic/</link><description>Recent content in Nordic on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/nordic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Durban Island</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</guid><description>&lt;p>Durban Island is a Canadian Arctic island located in Nunavut, Canada. It is one of Baffin Island&amp;rsquo;s northeast offshore islands within Davis Strait&amp;rsquo;s Merchants Bay. It is 36 km2 (14 sq mi) in size. Durban Harbour is on the island&amp;rsquo;s southeast facing side. Nearby can be found the larger Padloping Island, and Auyuittuq National Park Reserve is also to the west on Baffin Island.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Haifoss Waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</guid><description>&lt;p>The waterfall Háifoss is situated near the volcano Hekla in the south of Iceland. The river Fossá, a tributary of Þjórsá, drops here from a height of 122 m. This is the second highest waterfall of the island.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Leitisvatn Lake</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</guid><description>&lt;p>The name Leitisvatn means &amp;ldquo;The lake by Leiti&amp;rdquo; (the name of the east side of the lake). The lake is located very close to the ocean, but its surface is about 30 meters above the level of sea. It is surrounded by a higher cliff which prevents it from emptying into the ocean. The water exit is the waterfall Bøsdalafossur.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Odda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/odda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/odda/</guid><description>&lt;p>Odda municipality is very mountainous and the settlements are all located in valleys. Because of the many mountains, there are many large waterfalls including Låtefossen, Espelandsfossen, and Tyssestrengene. There are also many large lakes such as Sandvinvatnet, Votna, Valldalsvatnet, Røldalsvatnet, Ringedalsvatnet, Langavatnet, and parts of Ståvatn.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skógafoss</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</guid><description>&lt;p>Skógafoss is a waterfall situated on the Skógá River in the south of Iceland at the cliffs of the former coastline. After the coastline had receded seaward (it is now at a distance of about 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from Skógar), the former sea cliffs remained, parallel to the coast over hundreds of kilometres, creating together with some mountains a clear border between the coastal lowlands and the Highlands of Iceland.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>