<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rock on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/rock/</link><description>Recent content in Rock on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/rock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cappadocia</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</guid><description>&lt;p>In a spectacular landscape, entirely sculpted by erosion, the Göreme valley and its surroundings contain rock-hewn sanctuaries that provide unique evidence of Byzantine art in the post-Iconoclastic period. The density of its rock-hewn dwellings, churches, troglodyte villages and subterranean cities within the rock formations make it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most striking and largest cave-dwelling complexes. Though interesting from a geological and ethnological point of view, the incomparable beauty of the decor of the Christian sanctuaries makes Cappadocia one of the leading examples of the post-iconoclastic Byzantine art period, some dating back to the 4th century. Residents live in homes that are carved into the landscape. Cappadocia has a unique landscape that you will have never witnessed before in your lifetime. This makes it one of the most popular spots in the world to go up in a Hot Air Balloon.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Coober Pedy</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/coober-pedy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Coober Pedy is a town in southern Australia which around 150 million years ago was covered by ocean. When the water receded, the sandy silica minerals from the seabed flowed into the rocky cracks and cavities and solidified over time into the multi-coloured gem-stone, opal. Traditionally it has been a mining town ever since the discovery of opal, but the existing cavernous mines coupled with the intense heat outside made some people take a novel approach to building - going underground.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Danakil Depression</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</guid><description>&lt;p>The lowest and hottest place on earth, but you&amp;rsquo;re rewarded with amazing imagery of sulphurous lakes and geological creations. Remote, but worth it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Giant's Causeway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Giant&amp;rsquo;s Causeway is an area of about 40,000 interlocking basalt columns, the result of an ancient volcanic fissure eruption. It is located in County Antrim on the north coast of Northern Ireland, about three miles (4.8 km) northeast of the town of Bushmills.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hidden Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hidden-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hidden-beach/</guid><description>&lt;p>A gaping hole in the surface of the lush green island opens onto a secret beach, with ample shade, sun, and crystal-clear water.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hvítserkur</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hvítserkur is a 15 m high basalt stack along the eastern shore of the Vatnsnes peninsula, in northwest Iceland. The rock has two holes at the base, which give it the appearance of a dragon who is drinking. The base of the stack has been reinforced with concrete to protect its foundations from the sea. Several species of birds, such as gulls and fulmars, live on at Hvítserkur and its name (&amp;ldquo;white shirt&amp;rdquo; in Icelandic) comes from the color of the guano deposited on its rocks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Legzira Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</guid><description>&lt;p>The gigantic natural stone arches on this beach are indeed an amazing sight, although the beach itself is very rocky and as such does not lend itself well to sunbathing or swimming. Great for a walk though - the ocean is said to be as loud as an explosion when the waves crash against the rocks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Limone Sul Garda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nestled in the Italian Alps is Lake Garda, the largest lake in Italy. Around the lake there are a few quaint and very popular tourist towns including one called Limone (meaning Lemon in Italian). In addition to the surrounding beauty of the alps themselves, the town features an abundance of lemon trees which are as beautiful as the products made from them are delicious. Whether you want to buy some limoncello or enjoy some lemonade at a restaurant on the coast of the lake, this town is a must visit.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Petra Raqmu</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/petra-raqmu/</guid><description>&lt;p>Petra is a historical and archaeological city in southern Jordan that is famed for architecture carved directly into vibrant red, white, pink, and sandstone cliff faces. Originally known as Raqmu to the Nabataeans, Petra was the capital of the Nabataean empire until it was conquered and absorbed by the Roman Empire. The spectacular rock cut facades and innovative water conduit system found in Petra are monuments to the thriving and advanced civilization that once resided here.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>