<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nature on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/nature/</link><description>Recent content in Nature on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/nature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ausangate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ausangate/</guid><description>Also called &amp;ldquo;The Painted Mountains&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Rainbow Mountains&amp;rdquo; one look at them tells you where they get their name. These gorgeous pastel-colored mountains require a several day long trek through rough terrain, but it&amp;rsquo;s well worth it for the view!</description></item><item><title>Baatara gorge waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/baatara-gorge-waterfall/</guid><description>The Balaa gorge sinkhole (Baatara gorge waterfall) is a waterfall in the Tannourine, Lebanon near Balaa.
The waterfall drops 255 metres (837 ft) into the Balaa Pothole, a cave of Jurassic limestone located on the Lebanon Mountain Trail. The cave is also known as the Cave of the Three Bridges. Traveling from Laklouk to Tannourine one passes the village of Balaa, and the Three Bridges Chasm (in French Gouffre des Trois Ponts) is a five-minute journey into the valley below where one sees three natural bridges, rising one above the other and overhanging a chasm descending into Mount Lebanon.</description></item><item><title>Benagil Sea Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/benagil-sea-cave/</guid><description>The southern coast of Portugal is lined with exquisite beaches and caves, including the famous Benagil Sea Cave (skylight included).</description></item><item><title>Blue Grotto</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/blue-grotto/</guid><description>The Blue cave is located in the small bay of Balun on the island of Biševo.
It is 24 m long, 10-12 meters wide, 15 inches tall and 16 m deep. The entrance to the cave is about 1.5 m high and about 2.5 m wide with a long sea corridor.
The cave has two openings, one smaller, one artificially deepened, through which the boat can pass. The other opening is like a vault and much wider, on the south side of the cave, below the sea level.</description></item><item><title>Bolivian Salt Flats</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bolivian-salt-flats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bolivian-salt-flats/</guid><description>The reflective surface of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest salt mine is like something from the imagination of Salvador Dali.</description></item><item><title>Bonn</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/bonn/</guid><description>This German city has a fantastic display of cherry blossom trees when in season.</description></item><item><title>Cappadocia</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cappadocia/</guid><description>In a spectacular landscape, entirely sculpted by erosion, the Göreme valley and its surroundings contain rock-hewn sanctuaries that provide unique evidence of Byzantine art in the post-Iconoclastic period. The density of its rock-hewn dwellings, churches, troglodyte villages and subterranean cities within the rock formations make it one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most striking and largest cave-dwelling complexes. Though interesting from a geological and ethnological point of view, the incomparable beauty of the decor of the Christian sanctuaries makes Cappadocia one of the leading examples of the post-iconoclastic Byzantine art period, some dating back to the 4th century.</description></item><item><title>Cinque Terre</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/cinque-terre/</guid><description>The Cinque Terre (The Five Lands) is a rugged portion of coast on the Italian Riviera. The five lands comprises five villages: Monterosso al Mare, Vernazza, Corniglia, Manarola, and Riomaggiore. The coastline, the five villages, and the surrounding hillsides are all part of the Cinque Terre National Park (Parco Nazionale delle Cinque Terre). Over the centuries, people have carefully built terraces on the rugged, steep landscape right up to the cliffs that overlook the sea.</description></item><item><title>Danakil Depression</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/danakil-depression/</guid><description>The lowest and hottest place on earth, but you&amp;rsquo;re rewarded with amazing imagery of sulphurous lakes and geological creations. Remote, but worth it.</description></item><item><title>Durban Island</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/durban-island/</guid><description>Durban Island is a Canadian Arctic island located in Nunavut, Canada. It is one of Baffin Island&amp;rsquo;s northeast offshore islands within Davis Strait&amp;rsquo;s Merchants Bay. It is 36 km2 (14 sq mi) in size. Durban Harbour is on the island&amp;rsquo;s southeast facing side. Nearby can be found the larger Padloping Island, and Auyuittuq National Park Reserve is also to the west on Baffin Island.</description></item><item><title>Eilean Donan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/eilean-donan/</guid><description>Eilean Donan is a small tidal island where three lochs meet, Loch Duich, Loch Long and Loch Alsh, in the western Highlands of Scotland. A picturesque castle that frequently appears in photographs, film and television dominates the island, which lies about 1 kilometre (0.62 mi) from the village of Dornie. Since the castle&amp;rsquo;s restoration in the early 20th century, a footbridge has connected the island to the mainland.</description></item><item><title>Ellison's Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ellisons-cave/</guid><description>This pit cave is located on the Pigeon Mountain range on the Northwest of Georgia. It is the 12th deepest cave in the the US, extending over 12 miles and 1063 feet vertically. There are over 7 routes to reach the bottom of the cave.</description></item><item><title>French Southern Territories</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/french-southern-and-antarctic-lands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/french-southern-and-antarctic-lands/</guid><description>The Southern Lands consist of two archipelagos, Iles Crozet and Iles Kerguelen, and two volcanic islands, Ile Amsterdam and Ile Saint-Paul. They have no permanent inhabitants and are visited only by researchers studying the native fauna. The &amp;ldquo;Antarctic Lands&amp;rdquo; portion consists of Adelie Land, a thin slice of the Antarctic continent discovered and claimed by the French in 1840, and set aside by the Antarctic Treaty.</description></item><item><title>Giant's Causeway</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/giants-causeway/</guid><description>The Giant&amp;rsquo;s Causeway is an area of about 40,000 interlocking basalt columns, the result of an ancient volcanic fissure eruption. It is located in County Antrim on the north coast of Northern Ireland, about three miles (4.8 km) northeast of the town of Bushmills.</description></item><item><title>Ginnie Springs</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ginnie-springs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ginnie-springs/</guid><description>Located on the Santa Fe River in High Springs Florida, Ginnie Springs is one of the clearest springs in Florida. The 72-degree water is perfect for river tubing, swimming, snorkeling, scuba and cave diving.</description></item><item><title>Haifoss Waterfall</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/haifoss-waterfall/</guid><description>The waterfall Háifoss is situated near the volcano Hekla in the south of Iceland. The river Fossá, a tributary of Þjórsá, drops here from a height of 122 m. This is the second highest waterfall of the island.</description></item><item><title>Havasu Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/havasu-falls/</guid><description>Waterfall on the Havasupai Indian Reservation, known for swimming in a dramatic blue-green pool.</description></item><item><title>Hidden Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hidden-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hidden-beach/</guid><description>A gaping hole in the surface of the lush green island opens onto a secret beach, with ample shade, sun, and crystal-clear water.</description></item><item><title>Huang Shan</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/huang-shan-yellow-mountain/</guid><description>Huangshan (黄山, literally &amp;ldquo;Yellow Mountain&amp;rdquo;) is a mountain range in eastern China that is renowned for outstanding natural beauty, including ethereal seas of clouds, poetically named pines and rock formations, and hot springs with legendary histories. Huangshan is steeped in mythology and its beauty has inspired generations of Chinese artists. The mountain is also renowned for producing teas of high quality; it has been called one of China&amp;rsquo;s premier tea growing mountains.</description></item><item><title>Hvítserkur</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/hvitserkur/</guid><description>Hvítserkur is a 15 m high basalt stack along the eastern shore of the Vatnsnes peninsula, in northwest Iceland. The rock has two holes at the base, which give it the appearance of a dragon who is drinking. The base of the stack has been reinforced with concrete to protect its foundations from the sea. Several species of birds, such as gulls and fulmars, live on at Hvítserkur and its name (&amp;ldquo;white shirt&amp;rdquo; in Icelandic) comes from the color of the guano deposited on its rocks.</description></item><item><title>Hạ Long Bay</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ha-long-bay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ha-long-bay/</guid><description>Multiple tree-covered limestone islands dot this scenic diving, rock climbing &amp;amp; hiking destination.</description></item><item><title>Jade Mountain Resort</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jade-mountain-resort/</guid><description>On 243 hectares of lush tropical hillside, this high-end resort is set on Anse Chastanet Beach, overlooking the Caribbean Sea, and is 4 km from St. Lucia Botanical Gardens.</description></item><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Jökulsárlón Ice Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jokulsarlon-beach/</guid><description>Jökulsárlón (literally &amp;ldquo;glacial river lagoon&amp;rdquo;) is a large glacial lake in southeast Iceland, on the edge of Vatnajökull National Park. Situated at the head of the Breiðamerkurjökull glacier, it developed into a lake after the glacier started receding from the edge of the Atlantic Ocean. The lake has grown since then at varying rates because of melting of the glaciers. It is now 1.5 kilometres (0.93 mi) away from the ocean&amp;rsquo;s edge and covers an area of about 18 km2 (6.</description></item><item><title>Kuang Si Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuang-si-falls/</guid><description>The Kuang Si Falls, sometimes spelled Kuang Xi or known as Tat Kuang Si Waterfalls, is a three tier waterfall about 29 kilometres (18 mi) south of Luang Prabang. These waterfalls are a favourite side trip for tourists in Luang Prabang. The falls begin in shallow pools atop a steep hillside. These lead to the main fall with a 60 metres (200 ft)cascade. The falls are accessed via a trail to a left of the falls.</description></item><item><title>Kuramathi Island</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuramathi-island/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/kuramathi-island/</guid><description>Kuramathi is one of eight holiday resort islands owned and managed by Universal Enterprises Limited, a Maldivian company. There is a sandbank on the west of the island which is only visible when the tide is low.</description></item><item><title>Lake Bled</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lake-bled/</guid><description>According to a legend which stayed with the people, the temple of the ancient Slavic goddess Živa, once stood in the place of the present Baroque church. The temple disappeared during battles between the followers of the pagan religion and Christians, who destroyed the altar and built a church.</description></item><item><title>Lake Louise</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/louise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/louise/</guid><description>Lake Louise has become symbolic of the quintessentially Canadian mountain scene. This alpine lake, known for its sparkling blue waters, is situated at the base of impressive glacier-clad peaks that have long been at the heart of Canadian mountaineering. At about 2.5 kilometres long and 90 metres deep, the lake offers a surreal paddling experience in the warm summer months and one of the most scenic skating rinks in the world in winter.</description></item><item><title>Lauterbrunnen</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lauterbrunnen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lauterbrunnen/</guid><description>Lauterbrunnen is a small village in the Bernese Oberland region of Switzerland nestled between the towering walls of a sheer-sided valley that is famed for its waterfalls.</description></item><item><title>Legzira Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/legzira-beach/</guid><description>The gigantic natural stone arches on this beach are indeed an amazing sight, although the beach itself is very rocky and as such does not lend itself well to sunbathing or swimming. Great for a walk though - the ocean is said to be as loud as an explosion when the waves crash against the rocks.</description></item><item><title>Leitisvatn Lake</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/leitisvatn-lake/</guid><description>The name Leitisvatn means &amp;ldquo;The lake by Leiti&amp;rdquo; (the name of the east side of the lake). The lake is located very close to the ocean, but its surface is about 30 meters above the level of sea. It is surrounded by a higher cliff which prevents it from emptying into the ocean. The water exit is the waterfall Bøsdalafossur.</description></item><item><title>Limone Sul Garda</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/limone-sul-garda/</guid><description>Nestled in the Italian Alps is Lake Garda, the largest lake in Italy. Around the lake there are a few quaint and very popular tourist towns including one called Limone (meaning Lemon in Italian). In addition to the surrounding beauty of the alps themselves, the town features an abundance of lemon trees which are as beautiful as the products made from them are delicious. Whether you want to buy some limoncello or enjoy some lemonade at a restaurant on the coast of the lake, this town is a must visit.</description></item><item><title>Little Manitou Lake</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/little-manitou-lake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/little-manitou-lake/</guid><description>This mineral lake known for its healing powers is so buoyant it&amp;rsquo;s been dubbed the &amp;ldquo;Dead Sea of Canada.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Lungern</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lungern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/lungern/</guid><description>Nestled in the canton of Obwalden, on the road between Lucerne and Interlaken, you’ll find the mountain town of Lungern. This natural paradise, surrounded by mountain trails, is the perfect destination for nature lovers and hikers alike.</description></item><item><title>Mont Saint-Michel</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mont-saint-michel/</guid><description>A magical island topped by a gravity-defying medieval monastery, the Mont-Saint-Michel counts among France’s most stunning sights. For centuries one of Europe’s major pilgrimage destinations, this holy mount is now a UNESCO World Heritage Site, as is its breathtaking bay.</description></item><item><title>Mount Fuji</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mount-fuji/</guid><description>Mount Fuji, Japan, is one of the most famous mountains in the world. Mount Fuji is a composite cone, or stratovolcano. Composite cones, formed by violent eruptions, have layers of rock, ash, and lava.</description></item><item><title>Musandam Governorate</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/musandam/</guid><description>The Norway of the middle east, in the sense that it has super arid desert fjords dip straight into the sea. Feels a bit like another planet.</description></item><item><title>Mù Cang Chải</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/mu-cang-chai/</guid><description>Mù Cang Chải manages to be one of the most breathtaking spots in Vietnam, with terraced rice fields and mountainous landscapes.</description></item><item><title>Narai</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/narai/</guid><description>Located between Kiso Fukushima and Matsumoto, Narai-juku is one of the best-preserved post towns on Kiso&amp;rsquo;s Nakasendo Trail. Visit for a taste of the Japan of old.</description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/niagara-falls/</guid><description>Famous, towering waterfalls at the boundary of Canada &amp;amp; the United States, with tours &amp;amp; boat rides.</description></item><item><title>Ouzoud Falls</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/ouzoud-falls/</guid><description>Ouzoud Falls is the collective name for several tall waterfalls that empty into the El-Abid River gorge. This popular tourism destination is located near the Middle Atlas village of Tanaghmeilt, in the province of Azilal, 150 km northeast of Marrakech, Morocco.</description></item><item><title>Redwood National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</guid><description>At least once in your lifetime, you need to visit the magnificent coastal redwoods of Humboldt County - to walk, explore and soak up the silence and grandeur of forests unlike any others in the world. Whether your tastes run to scenic drives or hiking trails, you’ll find plenty of choices in Redwood National &amp;amp; State Parks in the north county, or along the Avenue of the Giants and Humboldt Redwoods State Park in south county.</description></item><item><title>Rigi</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/rigi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/rigi/</guid><description>Mount Rigi occupies a prominent place in the history of tourism. It has attracted tourists from around the world for nearly 150 years. Prior to 1871, people ascended Mount Rigi by foot or were carried in sedan chairs. In 1871, when the Rigi Railway from Vitznau started operating, reaching the summit of Mount Rigi became more comfortable and accessible for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Shitiping</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shitiping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/shitiping/</guid><description>Coastal spot popular for hiking &amp;amp; rock climbing, featuring a natural staircase of eroded stone.</description></item><item><title>Skógafoss</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/skogafoss-waterfall/</guid><description>Skógafoss is a waterfall situated on the Skógá River in the south of Iceland at the cliffs of the former coastline. After the coastline had receded seaward (it is now at a distance of about 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from Skógar), the former sea cliffs remained, parallel to the coast over hundreds of kilometres, creating together with some mountains a clear border between the coastal lowlands and the Highlands of Iceland.</description></item><item><title>Socotra</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/socotra/</guid><description>One of the most striking of Socotra&amp;rsquo;s plants is the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood tree (Dracaena cinnabari), which is a strange-looking, umbrella-shaped tree. Its red sap was thought to be the dragon&amp;rsquo;s blood of the ancients, sought after as a dye, and today used as paint and varnish. Also important in ancient times were Socotra&amp;rsquo;s various endemic aloes, used medicinally, and for cosmetics. Other endemic plants include the giant succulent tree Dorstenia gigas, the cucumber tree Dendrosicyos socotranus, the rare Socotran pomegranate, Aloe perryi, and Boswellia socotrana.</description></item><item><title>Sorrento Beach</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/sorrento-beach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/sorrento-beach/</guid><description>Sorrento is a township in Victoria, Australia, located on the shores of Port Phillip on the Mornington Peninsula, about one and a half hours by car south of Melbourne. It is a largely upper-class, seaside resort area, but is also a quiet seaside township in the off-peak months of the year. It was named by the Italian founders after the southern Italian town.</description></item><item><title>Stelvio Pass</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/stelvio-pass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/stelvio-pass/</guid><description>This famous paved mountain pass used by drivers &amp;amp; cyclists features dozens of hairpin turns.</description></item><item><title>Sơn Đoòng Cave</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/son-doong-cave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/son-doong-cave/</guid><description>According to the Limberts, the cave is five times larger than nearby caves like Phong Nha Cave and Hang En, the third largest cave in the world previously considered the biggest cave in Vietnam. The main passage in Sơn Đoòng is more than 5 kilometres (3.1 mi) long, 200 metres (660 ft) high and 150 metres (490 ft) wide.</description></item><item><title>Tegallalang Rice Terrace</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tegallalang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tegallalang/</guid><description>Scenic, terraced hillside offering rice paddies amid lush greenery, plus zip lines &amp;amp; jungle swings.</description></item><item><title>Valle de Cocora</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/valle-de-cocora/</guid><description>The wax palm, the Colombian national tree, is obviously the main attraction here. It is the tallest palm in the world, growing up to 60 meters, while retaining the girth of any old palm, making for a very slender giant, an immense pole topped with a little crown of palm fronds. Their wide root systems make for an odd visual: palms shooting up hundreds of feet into the sky, all widely but evenly spaced apart, as if planted purposefully.</description></item><item><title>Via Appia Antica</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/via-appia-antica/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/via-appia-antica/</guid><description>The Via Appica (Appian Way) was constructed in the 4th century B.C.; it is the reason we say all roads lead to Rome. The road is remarkably well preserved, its large flat paving stones polished by millennia of use and weathering, and standing as testament to the might of Roman engineering. Today the road is flanked on both sides by verdant fields punctuated with ruins and other vestiges of Roman history, with the occasional herds of grazing sheep adding to the sense of being transported back in time.</description></item><item><title>White Cliffs of Dover</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/dover/</guid><description>The White Cliffs of Dover are cliffs that form part of the English coastline facing the Strait of Dover and France. The cliffs are part of the North Downs formation. The cliff face, which reaches up to 350 feet (110 m), owes its striking façade to its composition of chalk accentuated by streaks of black flint. The cliffs spread east and west from the town of Dover in the county of Kent, an ancient and still important English port.</description></item></channel></rss>