<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Park on Wonderful World</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/park/</link><description>Recent content in Park on Wonderful World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/tags/park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jiu Zhai Gou</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/jiu-zhai-gou/</guid><description>Jiu Zhai Gou (九寨沟; literally &amp;ldquo;Valley of Nine Fortified Villages&amp;rdquo;) is a national park and nature reserve on the edge of the Tibetan plateau; its elevation ranges from 2,000 to 4,500 meters. The park is known for its many multi-level waterfalls, colorful lakes, musical rapids and snow-capped peaks. The park is also home to a number of endangered plant and animal species, including the giant panda and rare orchids.</description></item><item><title>Nara Deer Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/nara-deer-park/</guid><description>Nara Park (奈良公園, Nara Kōen) is a large park in central Nara. Established in 1880, it is the location of many of Nara&amp;rsquo;s main attractions including Todaiji, Kasuga Taisha, Kofukuji and the Nara National Museum. The park is home to hundreds of freely roaming deer. Considered in Shinto to be messengers of the gods, Nara&amp;rsquo;s nearly 1200 deer have become a symbol of the city and have even been designated as a natural treasure.</description></item><item><title>Palace of Versailles</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/palace-of-versailles/</guid><description>The Palace of Versailles (château de Versailles) is a royal château in Versailles, some 20 kilometers southwest of Paris. The palace was built for the Bourbon kings of France in the 17th century, fell into disrepair following the French revolution, and is now a museum and tourist attraction. The palace exemplifies the opulence of the Ancien Régime and the extensive gardens are one of the finest extant examples of French garden design.</description></item><item><title>Redwood National Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/redwood-national-park/</guid><description>At least once in your lifetime, you need to visit the magnificent coastal redwoods of Humboldt County - to walk, explore and soak up the silence and grandeur of forests unlike any others in the world. Whether your tastes run to scenic drives or hiking trails, you’ll find plenty of choices in Redwood National &amp;amp; State Parks in the north county, or along the Avenue of the Giants and Humboldt Redwoods State Park in south county.</description></item><item><title>Royal Palace of Caserta</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/royal-palace-of-caserta/</guid><description>The Royal Palace of Caserta (Italian: Reggia di Caserta) is a former royal residence in Caserta, southern Italy, constructed for the Bourbon kings of Naples during the 18th century. The palace is a UNESCO World Heritage Site; its nomination described it as &amp;ldquo;the swan song of the spectacular art of the Baroque, from which it adopted all the features needed to create the illusions of multidirectional space&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>San Martin Park</title><link>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/san-martin-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wonderfulworld.podrezo.com/san-martin-park/</guid><description>The Parque General San Martín is a park located in the city of Mendoza, Argentina.</description></item></channel></rss>